http://www.frommers.com/about/about_privacy

Thank you for subscribing!
Got it! Thank you!
Updated: June 26, 2018
FrommerMedia LLC (“Frommer’s”, “we” or “our”) understands that you are concerned about privacy, so we’ve provided this privacy notice (“Privacy Notice”) to disclose how we collect, use, share, and store your information. This Privacy Notice applies to our website (currently located at https://www.frommers.com), email, text, or other electronic messages between you and us, and other related services that we provide (“Services”). This Privacy Notice does not apply to information collected on sites, applications, destinations, or services linked to from our website or Services that we do not own or control.
Please read this Privacy Notice carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our website or our Services. By accessing or using our website or Services, you agree to this Privacy Notice. This Privacy Notice may change from time to time and your continued use of our website or the Services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the Privacy Notice periodically for updates.
Information We Collect and How We Collect It
Information You Provide
When you visit our website, we collect any contact information that you voluntarily provide to us on our Contact Us page, including your name and email address, in order to communicate in response to you. If you register on our website, we will collect your username and email address so that we may provide access to you to post on our forums or user blogs, monitor users’ compliance with our website, forum, or user blog policies, send communications to you about your registration or posts, and for other purposes set out in this Privacy Notice. If you apply for a job as an employee or independent contractor with us, we may require you to provide additional information including a resume and information required by law, in order to facilitate our evaluation or hiring of you, comply with applicable law, and for other purposes set out in this Privacy Notice. We also collect the personally identifiable information that you choose to post in our forums or user blogs on our website in order to monitor users’ compliance with our website, forum, or user blog policies, improve our content and Services, and for other purposes set out in this Privacy Notice. We also collect any other personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide when you communicate with us including personal correspondence such as emails or any other activity through which you identify yourself in order to send communications to you, improve our content and Services, and for other purposes set out in this Privacy Notice. To the extent we are able to do so, we may link your non-personally identifiable information with your personally identifiable information. We may also link information collected online with information we collect offline or information collected online by third parties.
Automated Collection
While you browse our website, we may collect information, that by itself typically cannot be used to identify or contact you, through the use of cookies or other now known or later developed technologies to assist us in observing the behavior of users visiting our website or using our Services. Such information may include your web browser type and browser language, internet protocol address, device information (including type, specifications, settings, and operating system), geographic location, and, in addition to information on where you arrived from, navigational actions you may take on our website or our Services such as which pages you view and which links you click. When you visit our website, we collect information to help select advertising that we believe is more relevant to you, including information about what advertisements have already been displayed to and seen by you.
Cookies: A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. If you wish to limit, block or delete cookies from our website – or any other website - you can use your browser to do this. Each browser is different so check the ‘Help’ menu of your particular browser or the browser settings for your mobile device to learn how to change your cookie preferences.
If you do this, however, certain features of our website may not work correctly or cannot be provided to you. For more information about our use of cookies, please read our Cookie Policy.
Web beacons (tracking pixels): Web beacons (also known as tracking pixels) are bits of data that count the number of users who access a website or open an email and can also allow us to see if a cookie has been activated. Web beacons used on web pages or in emails allow us to see how successful an article has been, or whether an email message was successfully delivered and read in a marketing campaign. We also use web beacons to learn if you have clicked on any links or advertisements contained in emails. We may use this information to help us identify which emails are more interesting to you and to inform advertisers how many customers have clicked on their advertisements (the information shared with advertisers is aggregated and does not identify you individually).
Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some content, including advertisements or videos, on our website is served by third parties, including advertisers, advertising networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies, alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. Their collection of information is governed by their privacy notices. Please read our Cookie Policy for more information about third parties that collection information from you on our website and links to privacy notices and opt-outs. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.
How We Use Your Information
We may use the information collected from you:
to present our website and its contents to you;
to provide the Services to you;
to improve the content of our website or our Services, including our advertising;
to enhance users' experiences when visiting our website or using our Services;
to customize the content and layout of our website or our Services for a customer or for each individual user;
to provide you with information about our Services that you request from us;
to provide you with notices about your account or your newsletter subscription;
to send you targeted messages, publications, news, or information about events, special offers, promotions or benefits;
to display advertising to you that we believe is relevant to your interests, understand which advertising is more interesting to you, and identify which advertisers or advertising networks display advertising that is most interesting to you;
to use third-party service providers to send and distribute e-mail and to perform other marketing and support functions on our behalf or otherwise to assist us in providing our Services to you;
to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;
to notify you about changes to our website or any Services we offer or provide;
to allow you to participate in interactive features on our website or Services;
for identity management, security, and auditing;
for any other purpose for which you provide it; or
in any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
Sharing Your Information
Except as disclosed in this Privacy Notice, we do not share, rent, or sell personally identifiable information you have given us to any third party without your permission. We rely on service providers to help us deliver our Services. We may provide your personal information to service providers or contractors to perform functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, communicating news; performing website or Services development or maintenance; providing functionality or other services for our website and our Services; sending postal mail, email or other communications; removing outdated and repetitive information from our lists; analyzing our data, developing, enhancing, marketing or providing any of our Services; processing payments; or assisting us with other marketing and support functions.
During the course of our business we may also share with third parties aggregated demographic and statistical information that is not personally identifiable.
We may also disclose an individual's personal information:
to a person who in our reasonable judgment is seeking the information as an agent of the individual or company;
if, in our reasonable judgment, it is necessary enforce compliance with our internal policies or the agreement for our Services; or to protect our website, Services, customers, or others;
in situations where sharing or disclosing your information is required in order to provide you with information that you have requested;
in connection with a legal action or other proceeding, including without limitation, in response to a court order or a subpoena;
in response to a law enforcement agency's request;
to another entity as part of a merger, bankruptcy, a sale of assets or all or part of a business, or any other corporate change or re-organization; or
to a third party or parties, where the individual consents to such disclosure or disclosure is required or permitted by law.
Marketing Opt-Out
You can opt-out of receiving our newsletter (including the marketing and promotional emails) from us at any time by selecting the opt-out link included in the email or by responding by email that you no longer wish to receive the newsletter. Although we strive to update our email list as frequently as possible, you might receive another contact before we are able to remove you. If you have previously opted out of receiving emails from us and wish to reverse this decision, please contact us, we’ll be happy to get your name back on the list to receive electronic communications from us. Please note that even if you opt-out of receiving our newsletter, you will continue to receive communications as it pertains to your account. We may use any of your contact information held on file (including email address, mailing address, telephone or facsimile numbers) to communicate with you about general administrative business such as support questions, Services alerts, or other administrative purposes.
Children's Information
Our website is not intended for children under the age of 16. In particular, we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information on our website from children under the age of 16 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we learn that, despite these measures, a child under the age of 16 has submitted personally identifiable information to us through our website, we will take reasonable measures to delete such information from our records and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required by law).
How We Store Your Information
We are committed to protecting the security of any personal information you provide to us. We maintain commercially reasonable safeguards to maintain the security and privacy of personal information that you provide to us. In spite of these protections, we cannot guarantee the security of any data submitted over or stored on the internet. After your information reaches us, however, it is stored on servers protected by procedures and technology designed to block reasonably foreseeable intrusions by unauthorized third parties. After you have submitted your information online to us, we recommend that you end your browser session before leaving your computer.
Third-Party Websites
This Privacy Notice applies solely to information collected by us. This Privacy Notice does not apply to other websites that are accessible through our website. Please be aware that third-party websites that are accessible through our website or our Services (including social media websites) may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites and will not be responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit.
Do Not Track
Some web browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature. This feature lets you tell websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. These features are not yet uniform across browsers nor is there a common agreement about how to implement these features or interpret user intent. Our Services are not currently set up to respond to those signals.
Correcting or Updating Your Information
If you would like to request changes to your personally identifiable information that you have previously provided to us, please contact us using the contact information below.
Additional Notice to Residents of the European Economic Area (EEA) and Switzerland
Legal Bases for Collection and Processing of Information
Our collection and processing of your personally identifiable information is supported by a number of legal bases. Set out below are the most relevant ones. Please note that while we may rely on one legal basis for a particular activity, if that is no longer applicable or available then we may be able to rely on another basis.
With Your Consent: We collect and process some of your personally identifiable information because we obtain your consent. When we want to use cookies, to collect personally identifiable information from you for performance or marketing reasons, for example, we obtain your consent by displaying a banner when you first visit our website (or, if you have deleted your cookies, when you next visit) that discloses the reasons we use cookies to collect information and links to our Cookie Policy, which in turn contains more detailed information about our collection, third-party collection, and opt-out information. You must accept the use of those cookies or you may not visit or use our website. Another example is when we want to send our newsletter to you, which includes marketing material, we obtain your consent first and you may opt-out of receiving that newsletter at any time.
To Fulfill a Contract: We collect and process some of your personally identifiable information because we need to do so either to enter into or fulfill a contract we have with you. For example, we process your personally identifiable information when we provide products to you that you have purchased on our website.
For a Legitimate Interest: We may process your personally identifiable information where we or a third party have a legitimate interest in doing so. For example, we have a legitimate interest in understanding how people are using our Services, both to improve them and to sell advertising more effectively. Therefore, we may use your personally identifiable information to understand and analyze your use of our Services. When we rely on our legitimate interest, we will carry out a balancing test between our legitimate interests and your privacy rights. Our legitimate interests include: understanding how our audience interacts with our content, our advertising, and our Services; learning about our audience in order to improve our Services for them; developing, delivering, and maintaining relevant and engaging content and advertising; supporting reporting on topics of interest to individuals and the community; supporting individuals’ rights to receive information; and conducting our business activities and achieving our business goals.
To Comply with Legal Obligations: We will process your personally identifiable information when necessary to comply with legal and regulatory obligations or defend claims. For example, we may share your personally identifiable information in response to a court order, subpoena, or law enforcement agency's request.
Retention of Information
We will only keep your personally identifiable information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected and processed, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, regulatory, accounting, or reporting requirements.
To determine the appropriate retention period for your personally identifiable information, we will consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personally identifiable information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure, the purposes for which we process it (and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means), and the applicable legal requirements.
In some circumstances we may anonymize your personally identifiable information so that it can no longer be associated with you, in which case it is no longer personally identifiable information.
Upon expiration of the applicable retention period we will securely destroy your personal data in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.
Access, Correction and Deletion of Information
For personally identifiable information that we hold about you, you may have the right (subject to exceptions allowed by law) to:
request access to your personally identifiable information;
request we correct any inaccurate personally identifiable information;
request we delete any personally identifiable information;
restrict the processing of personally identifiable information;
object to the processing of personally identifiable information; and/or
receive a copy of your personally identifiable information in a structured and commonly used machine-readable format or have such personally identifiable information transmitted to another company.
We may ask you for additional information to confirm your identity and for security purposes, before disclosing information requested to you.
Transfer of Information
We are located in the United States and your personally identifiable information that we collect is processed and stored in the United States. We rely on derogations for specific situations as set forth in Article 49 of the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). In particular, we collect and transfer to the United States personally identifiable information with your consent; to perform a contract with you; or to fulfill a compelling legitimate interest of ours in a manner that does not outweigh your rights and freedoms. The United States has not sought nor received a finding of “adequacy” from the European Union under Article 45 of the GDPR. Given the lack of a finding of “adequacy”, there may be a risk that the supervisory authority and/or data processing principles and/or data subject rights in the United States might not be sufficiently appropriate or comprehensive safeguards from the perspective of the EU. We strive, however, to apply suitable safeguards to protect the privacy and security of your personally identifiable information and only to use it consistent with your relationship with us and the practices described in this Privacy Notice. Our vendors are either certified to the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks or we use Standard Contractual Clauses that have been provided by the EU Commission in our agreements with them.
Privacy Notice Changes
We may amend this Privacy Notice from time to time. Should this Privacy Notice be amended in any way, changes will be posted to this webpage. As we may make changes from time to time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Notice. Your continued use of our website or our Services after the effective date of any modification to the Privacy Notice will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms.
Contact Us
Questions regarding this Privacy Notice should be directed to Frommer’s:
through the Contact Us page on our website
or by email at Legal@frommermedia.com
advertisement
advertisement
Get Inspired for Your Next Vacation
Frommer's, and carefully selected third parties, use cookies on this site to improve performance, for analytics and for advertising. By browsing this site, you consent to the placement of these cookies. For more information see our Cookie Policy.
I accept
Destinations
All Regions
Asia
Australia & South Pacific
Caribbean & Atlantic
Central & South America
Europe
Washington, D.C.
Great Vacation Ideas in the U.S.A.
